Bigger is a drama, history film directed by George Gallo.
The inspirational tale of the grandfathers of the fitness
movement as we now know it, Joe & Ben Weider.
Battling anti-Semitism, racism and extreme poverty, the brothers beat
all odds to build an empire & inspire future generations.
Joe Weider, played by Tyler Hoechlin.
Ben Weider, played by Aneurin Barnard.
Jack Lalanne, played by Colton Haynes.
Betty Weider, played by Julianne Hough.
Michael Steere, played by DJ Qualls.
Kathy Weider, played by Victoria Justice.
Bigger (styled as Bigger: The Joe Weider Story) is a 2018 American comedy drama film by
director George Gallo about the life of real life bodybuilders Joe and Ben Weider.
The film explores themes of based on true story,
bodybuilding, bodybuilder, brother brother relationship.
The tone is emotional.